patentstorm.us 2008-12-18

# PatentStorm - Privacy Policy

###  Bizarre Patents 

Patent No. 5307162

Cloaking System Using Optoelectronically Controlled Camouflage 

A Cloaking System designed to operate in the visible light spectrum, utilizes optoelectronics and/or photonic components to conceal an object within it.

###  Newsletter

To be informed of important news about our site, enter your email here. You can always unsubscribe later. Your address will not be released to others. (Read our Privacy Policy) 

### Privacy

PatentStorm respects privacy and understands that web site users do not want their email and other personal information to be distributed to others. 

**Information collection**

PatentStorm uses cookies to collect non-identifiable information about each user's travels on the site in order to analyze patterns of use on the site. 

This information will be used only for statistical purposes and will not be used to monitor the specific requests by identifiable individuals. 

**Information distribution**

PatentStorm will never sell, rent or otherwise disclose personally identifiable information to any 3rd party for the purpose of marketing or solicitation or other information gathering. 

We believe it is necessary, and we reserve the right, to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of PatentStorm's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 

**Communications with Customers**

At present PatentStorm only contacts its users who have opted-in to our email system notifying them of major new features of the site. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

PatentStorm may update this policy. 

We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in PatentStorm account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.
